NIKITA GUPTA

Company Secretary B.Com

Company Secretary with more than 4 years of Post Qualification experience in managing corporate laws including secretarial compliances along with other Regulatory Laws having experience of working in firm as well as corporate industry.

In my spare time, I love to read and write articles on creating a simplified life for handling busy routines in an organized way so that people who are engrossed in so much work commitments and responsibilities could find time for things they enjoy the most.

inlinkedin.com/in/cs-nikita-gupta

91-8057946821

n.nikitagupta.g@gmail.com

Supertech Capetown, Sector- 74, Noida- 201301

SOFTWARE SKILLS

MS Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Tally ERP and Designing of Marketing Collaterals such as Corporate Brochures, Letter Heads etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pashupati Polytex (P) Ltd Company Secretary 16th April, 2019- Present Kashipur

- Filing of various forms with ROC under new Companies Act;
- Preparation of minutes of Board, its committees and members meeting;
- Maintenance of Statutory Registers;
- Preparation and vetting of various agreements including consulting agreements, Joint venture agreements, vendor Agreement, MOU, Non- Disclosure Agreement, Shareholders Agreement, etc:
- Handled compliances related to EPR obligations for recycling company under Plastic Waste Management Rules, 2016;
- Vetting of accounts and financials of company.

M/s Siddarth Agarwal & Co Senior Associate 19th February, 2018-15th March, 2019 Noida

- Handled Private Placement issues and its compliances under Companies Act;
- Incorporation of Companies;
- Preparation & filing of ITR returns;
- Preparation of articles on various topics under Corporate and taxation laws.

M/s Kriti Advisory Services Private Limited (KAS) Manager

Kaushambi, Ghaziabad

25th January 2017 - 10th February, 2018

- Handled and prepared the various charges documents and its compliances of the Financial Service company BARCLAYS;
- Handled allotment of shares and payment of Stamp Duty thereon;
- Conducted Secretarial Audit for various infrastructure, listed and Real Estate Companies including GMR Group, C & C Constructions Limited, Sterling Tools Limited, Rapid Metro Rail Gurgaon Limited and its group Companies, etc);
- Preparation of Search Report;
- Handled day to day Statutory compliances of listed and unlisted Companies;
- Preparation and filing of Statutory documents viz. Board Report, annual return etc for both listed and unlisted Companies;
- Handled E-Voting and Preparation of Consolidated Scrutinizer Report for E- Voting and Postal Ballot;
- Reporting of Financials in XBRL of listed and unlisted companies;
- Handled annual and other compliances of LLPs;
- Conducted SEBI Audits of RTA under LODR Regulations, 2015;
- Preparation and Submission of Corporate Governance report, Shareholding pattern etc under Listing guidelines;
- Preparation of Trademark Application and submission of Replies pursuant to the Objections;
- Compliance under FEMA 1999 with respect to foreign remittances including allotment of shares.

EDUCATION

- CS from ICSI in 2015
- B.Com from Kumaun University in 2013
- 12th from CBSE in 2010
- 10th from CBSE in 2008